pokerworks.com 2017-12-12

# PokerWorks Privacy Policy | PokerWorks

Your privacy is very important to iBus Media Ltd. (referred to herein as **“PokerWorks”** , “ **we** ” or “ **us** ”), the owner and operator of the website located at [www.pokerworks.com](http://pokerworks.com/) as well as the local sites there under, listed here (collectively, the “ **Site** ”). We are committed to maintaining the confidentiality of the personal information collected by us in order to allow you to enjoy your use of the Site by safeguarding it and utilizing appropriate software and hardware architecture, techniques, methods and procedures as customary in the industry. 

* **Consent to Privacy Policy**

By using the Site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy and changes and you can determine when the Privacy Policy was last modified by checking the "Last updated" legend at the bottom of the Privacy Policy. If the policies described in our Privacy Policy change in any material respect, we will notify you by posting the revised policy on our Site, by email, or by other means that we may choose and as required by applicable law. We may apply changes to information previously collected by us, to the extent permitted by law. If you do not agree to be bound by the terms of the new or modified Privacy Policy, you agree to immediately notify us that your personal information should be deleted. Your continued use of the Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any amendments. Our [Terms of Use](http://pokerworks.com/%7B!link:page%7Cterms-conditions%7D) found take precedence over any conflicting provision of this Privacy Policy. Unless otherwise defined herein, capitalized terms shall have the meaning given to them in our Terms of Use. Please further note section 4 of this Privacy Policy that details specific terms applicable in connection with our bonus programs and promotions. To the extent there is any conflict between the general terms of this Privacy Policy and the terms of section 4 below, the terms of section 4 shall prevail.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to enable you to understand how we collect, store, use and safeguard your personal information and for you to understand your rights in relation to that information.

* **What Personal information is collected and for what purpose**

As part of the Site account opening process and to allow us to provide services to you, we will ask you to provide us with a user name, email address and a password. In some cases we may also ask you to provide certain personal information such as your full name, date of birth, country of residence, and Twitter and Facebook user names.

We, members of our corporate group, our affiliates and third parties providing services on our behalf will use your personal information described above for various purposes such as:

  * to provide information and/or services to you;
  * identification and verification purposes;
  * statistical analysis and research;
  * research and development;
  * marketing, market research and customer profiling;
  * data analysis; and
  * to comply with licensing and regulatory requirements.

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or by regulatory authority and/or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary:

  * to comply with any law or comply with legal process served on us;
  * to protect and defend our rights or property;
  * to any regulatory body or licensing body or authority;
  * to third parties who provide services to us or on our behalf; 
  * to any third party that purchases us or our business or any part of us or our business; 
    * with your consent;
    * for the purposes of disaster recovery; or
    * as set out in Section 6 below.

Your personal information may be processed by us, other members of our corporate group, our affiliates, our agents and third parties providing services to us, in any jurisdiction and we will use all reasonable commercial efforts to comply with the terms of any data protection laws applicable to our activities.

We will only use your name in publicity materials with your consent.

It is very important that you complete the account details with valid information, since it will be used for the aforementioned purposes. You are required to advise us of any relevant changes to your personal information, if and where applicable.

* **Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

We may use “cookies” on or in connection with our Site to maintain information about you. A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. We use both “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. When you visit our Site, our computer may ask your computer for permission to employ the use of a session or persistent cookie. Our Site will then send a cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits our Site to access the cookies it has already sent to you and not the cookies sent to you by other websites. Many web browsers can be adjusted to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, our Site or certain areas or features of our Site. A more detailed explanation of our cookie policy [can be found here](http://pokerworks.com/cookies-information.htm).

Our servers automatically collect data about your Internet Protocol address when you visit us. When you request pages from our Site, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our server may also record the referring page that linked you to us (e.g., another website or a search engine); the pages you visit on our Site; the website you visit after this Site; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Site or a referral website; and other web usage activity and data logged by our web servers. Your IP address can also be used for moderation purposes, in order to limit the creation of multiple accounts and SPAM prevention.

When you use the Site, we may employ clear gifs (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make the Site better for our users.

* **Special Promotions Privacy Terms**

PokerWorks may, from time to time, initiate certain bonus programs and other promotional activities (collectively, the " **Promotions** "), in connection with which certain additional personal information may be collected from our users. Specifically, the personal information that may be collected in connection with our Promotions includes a user's name, surname, room nickname (i.e. the nickname the user gives him/herself in connection with the specific Promotion), email address, and country of residence. In addition, in certain Promotions as well as in certain cases in which further verification procedures so require, a user may also be asked to provide a telephone number and a facial photograph together with the user's ID. 

PokerWorks may disclose the personal information described above to such third parties with whom PokerWorks partners in connection with the Promotions. 

* **Confidentiality**

PokerWorks undertakes appropriate efforts to protect the confidentiality of the identity, preferences and other information it collects about users of the Site and other than as specified in this Privacy Policy, it will not knowingly allow access to this information to anyone outside PokerWorks. 

You should also do your part in protecting your information. Your login credentials are confidential and you are obliged to keep your login credentials secret and confidential at all times and to take all efforts to protect their secrecy and confidentiality.

Please be advised, however, that due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, the security of user information may be compromised at any time. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. 

* **Limits of Confidentiality**

Due to the legal, regulatory and security environment in which we operate, PokerWorks may be required, under certain circumstances, to disclose personally identifiable information of our users and we may not be permitted to inform you that we have done so. PokerWorks will use reasonable endeavours to limit such disclosure where PokerWorks believes in good faith that it is required to do so in response to a subpoena, warrant or other legal process, or where reasonably necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against persons or entities to preserve and/or enforce PokerWorks' rights. Further, we can, and you authorize us to, disclose your user identification information to third party agents of PokerWorks or official government bodies as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or other unlawful activity or activity that may expose us to legal liability.

* **Who receives your information?**

In addition to legally required disclosures as explained in this Privacy Policy, we may disclose your personal information to our employees, employees of other companies in our corporate group, our agents and to third party service providers who use your personal information to provide services to us in respect of your being a user of PokerWorks. All recipients of your personal information shall be bound by applicable data protection laws to keep your personal information private.

* **Your rights in relation to your information**

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. You can write to us at any time to review, change, obtain a copy of your information or have your details altered or corrected in accordance with your rights under applicable laws, and in such event we may require evidence of your identity. In order to contact us regarding your information please contact us. We may in certain circumstances levy a small charge to cover the cost of administration regarding any request made by you in this regard.

* **Links**

The Site may contain links to third parties' websites. While we attempt to provide links to sites that value your privacy, we cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policies of such sites. We encourage you to carefully review the privacy policies of such third parties' websites prior to any use of such websites.

* **Opt-Out Options**

We and other members of our corporate group may occasionally send you emails with information on events and news or information regarding new services or in connection with customer support matters. If you no longer wish to receive our email newsletters, you can opt-out, at any time, by [contacting us](http://pokerworks.com/contact-us.html) requesting removal of your email address from any such mailing lists. If applicable, you may also opt-out from receiving marketing communications from us by following instructions on our email communications explaining how to unsubscribe from our email mailing lists. We will take appropriate steps to fulfill your request within reasonable time; however, it may take a few days or longer to process your request during which you may still receive marketing communications from us. We reserve the right to send you non-marketing notice about your account, even if you opt-out of all email notifications.

If you decide to terminate your account with us, you may do so by [contacting us](http://pokerworks.com/contact-us.html) specifying your request and providing us with your PokerWorks Username and email address with which you registered. If you terminate your account, your profile will be removed from the Site, however, deletion may not be immediate and we may continue keeping your personal information in our records for audits and other administrative purposes.

* **Who are we?**

iBus Media Limited  
4th Floor Exchange House  
54-58 Athol Street  
Douglas  
Isle of Man  
IM1 1JD
